Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 3: Boxes 45-48
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 3: Boxes 45-48
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 3: Boxes 45-48
5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
48 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into three sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22 (box 21 has not been inventoried at this time)
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-48
Subjects:
Automation.; Automobile industry and trade.; Boycotts.; Casual labor.; Child labor.; Coal trade.; Collective bargaining.; Labor disputes.; Economic history.; Vocational education.; Electronic data processing.; Employees--Attitudes.; Discrimination in employment.; Agricultural laborers.; Public contracts.; Collective bargaining -- Government employees.; Hours of labor.; Industrial relations; Job analysis; Job descriptions; Labor laws and legislation; Labor mobility; Labor unions; Labor unions and international relations; Labor unions--Political activity; Free enterprise; Profit-sharing; Railroads; Social security--Law and legislation; Textile industry; Clothing trade; Employees--Training of; Wages; Incentives in industry; Job satisfaction
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents); Publications (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
CONTAINER LIST
- Box 45, Folder (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Kellogg's Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
    Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Kellog's Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Working Together at kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Say, I've got an Idea for Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Welcome to Kellogg's of Battle Creek, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Master Agreement Kellogg Company and American Federatio of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Master Agreement Kellogg company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Supplemental Agreement Between Kellogg Company and Local No. 3 American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Supplemental Agreement Between Kellogg Company and Local No. 3 American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Agreement Between Kellogg Company and Printing Speciality and Paper Products Union, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: contract Between Kellogg Company and Local No. 3 American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Agreement Between Kellogg Company and Printing Specialty and Paper Products Union Local No. 480, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Straight Talk, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Kellogg Company Cooperative Engineering Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Kellogg's Profit Sharing With You!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Kellogg's Profit Sharing With You!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Kellogg's Profit Sharing With You!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: Straight Talk, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Kellog Annual, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Kellogg Annual Album, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Kellogg News Annual, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Kellogg Company Policy-- Reimbursement of Cost Outside Study Courses Enrolled in by Kellogg Employees, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: The Best to You Each Morning from Kellogg, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: W. K. Kellogg Foundation, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Brief Statement Kellogg Company -- Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Kellogg's Profit Sharing With You!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Equal Employment Opportunity Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Inide Straight Talk, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Straight talk, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: Kellogg Annual 1973, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Kellogg's 1973 Annual report, Publication (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Box 45, Folder (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: History of the League for Industrial Rights, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
    By Walter Gordon Merritt. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Law and Labor, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Law and Labor, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Law and Labor, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The National Labor relations Board, Publication (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Box 45, Folder (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: LID Pamphlets Series, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Industrial democracy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: LID Summer School, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Supplementary Reading on current Social and Economic Problems, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: LID: Its Activities and a Look Ahead, Publication (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Box 45, Folder (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: They Struck the Dagger into the Back of Labor, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: How to organize a Local Political Campaign, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Who Causes Strikes?, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: No Amendments, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Support Fair Labor Standards in Industry!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Labor's Non-partisan League, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Employee Plan of the Leeds & Northrup Co., Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
    By Morris Leeds. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Democratic Organization in the Leeds and Northrup Company, Inc, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: To All State and Local Officers of Labor's Npn-partisan League, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Special Rules of Order of L& N Council, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Constitution of the Leeds & Northup Cooperative Association, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Is labor Riding for A Fall?, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Factory in a Warehouse, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Lincoln's Incentive System and Approach to Manufacturing, Publication (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Box 45, Folder (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Council Plan of Employees and management, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: General Council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Minutes: General Council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Minutes: General council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Minutes: General Council Meetings, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: General council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Minutes General Council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Minutes: General Council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Minutes: General Council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Minutes: General Council Meeting, Publication (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Box 45, Folder (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Agreement With Federation of Telephone Employees of Michigan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Agreement With the Commercial Telephone Workers Association of michigan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Employee Induction and Training Program, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Publication for Employees, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Employee Organizations and Activities, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Payroll Deductions for Employee Savings, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Employees' Payroll Allotment Plan for United States Defense Savings Bonds, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Memorandum covering the Handling of Employees Returning from Military Leaves of Asence, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Constitution of the Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Pyroll Deduction Plan for national service Life Insurance Preminums, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Agreement With the Michigan Telephone Employees Federation, Inc., Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Health and Safety Programs, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Employment Tests, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Agreement With the Michigan Telephone Employees Federation, Inc., Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 15: The Employes' Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: Constitution of Plant Employees Association, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: Michigan Bell Telephone company Traffic Department, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Employee Representation Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: Employes' Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: Telephone Employees Credit Union by-Laws, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: A Safety Code for Plant Employees, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: Working Agreement, Publication (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Box 45, Folder (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Contract Between Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Contract Between Kellogg Compnay and the American Federation of Grai Processors, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Contract Between Kellogg Company and the American Federation of Grain Processors, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: contract Between Kellogg Company of Canada Ltd. And the International Chemical Workers Union - Local No. 171, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Contract Between Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Contract Between Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: contract Between Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Agreement Between Kellogg Company and Kellogg Printing Pressment and Assistants union No. 480, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Financial and Statistical Report, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Hospital and Surgical Care Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: Two and One-Half Years Under the Six-Hour Say, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: Getting Acquainted with kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Your Future with Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Your Future with Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Welcome to Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: Welcome to Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: You and Your Job at Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: Kellogg's Hospital and Surgical Insurance Underwritten by Traveller Insurance Company, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: kellogg's Battle Creek Plant Newsletter, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Federal Credit Unions, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: Constitution and By-Laws of the Kellogg Twenty-Five Year Club, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: Kellogg Company Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: Kellogg Company Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 25: You and Your Job at Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 26: Warehouse Working Rules, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 27: Kellogg Profits and You, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 28: Facts About Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 29: Facts About kellogg's of Battle Creek, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 30: Agreement Between Kellogg Companya and Kellogg Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 31: Welcome to Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 32: Kellogg Company Policy -- Reimbursement of Cost of Outside Study courses Enrolled in by Kellogg Employees, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 33: Kellogg News, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 34: Kellogg's Profit Sharing With You!, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 35: Working Together at Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 36: Savings and Retirement Fund, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 37: Personnel Relations Division, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 38: Company Personnel Forms, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 39: Contract Between Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 40: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 41: contract Between Kellogg company and American Federation of grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 42: Agreement Between Kellogg Company and Printing Speciality and paper Products Union, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 43: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 44: Kellogg's is People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 45: contract between Kellogg Company and American Federation of grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 46: Contract Between Kellogg Company and American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 47: checj List for New Hourly Rated personnel, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 48: Check List for Employee Leaving the Kellogg Co., Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 49: I'll Invest My Money in People, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 50: Say I've Gor an Idea for Kellogg's, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 51: Kellogg's of Battle Creek, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 52: Kellogg company Training Policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 53: Education Policy - Tuition Refund policy, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 54: Exit Interview Report, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Item 55: 1966 Kellogg News Photo contest Winner, Publication (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Box 46, Folder (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Health, Meical, Dental, Life Insurance and Military Agreements, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Health, Meical, Dental, Life Insurance and Military Agreements, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: To All Bargained for Employees Whose Job Titles are Covered by the Comptroller's Operations, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Health, Meical, Dental, Life Insurance and Military Agreements, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Agreement Effective Octobe, 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Health, Meical, Dental, Life Insurance and Military Agreements, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Collective Bargaining Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: collective Bargaining Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Wage Guides for Weekly Rated Non-management Employees, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Collective Bargaining Agreement Business Services, Dining Service, Operator Services, Operations Staff, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Facilities Metro Operations Staff Installtion and Repair Mail Services Operations Staff Public Telephone, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Facilities Metro Operations Staff Installation and Repair Mail Service, Network Services, Operation Staff, Public Telephone, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Collective Bargaining Agreement Business Services Dining Services, Operator Services, Operations Staff, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Agreement Effective October 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Collective Bargaining Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Collective Bargaining Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Switching Systems Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Agreement Effective October 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: Wage Reopener Agreement Effective September 23, 1965, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Agreement Effective October 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Agreement Effective October 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: Agreement Effective October 2, 1968, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Collective Bargaining Agreement Traffic Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: 1965 Wage Reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Collective Bargaining Agreement, Plant Department Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: Collective Bargaining Agreement Switching Systems Department, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: Agreement Effective October 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 28: Agreement Effective October 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: 1965 Wage reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 30: Consolidation of the Foregoing Departmental Agreements for the Everyday Convenience of Employees, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 31: Collective Bargaining Agreement Comptroller's Operations, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Agreement Effective October 2, 1966, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 33: Collective Bargaining Agreement Effective August 10, 1980, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 34: Collective bargaining Agreement, Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 35: Benefits Agreements, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 36: To All Bargained for Employees, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 37: Pick a Career with Michigan Bell, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 38: 44th Pioneer Assembly: Serving People is Our Goal, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Item 39: Filing Claims Under the Company's Extraordinary Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Box 46, Folder (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Lower Rates on Interstate Calls Announced, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Attendance Control, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Automation and the Bell System, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
    By Clifton Phalen. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Medical Department Survey, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: The world's Telephones, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Challenge Opportunity, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: A Future for You in the Telephone Business, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Telephone Jobs for High School Graduates, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Development of Operators, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefots and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Employee Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: The Service Assistant's Bulletin, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Let's Talk it Over with Mom and Dad, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Extraordinary Medical Expense Plan, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Low Cost Group Life Insurance, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Plan for Employees' Pensions Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: The Men who Direct, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Films for Your Women's Group, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Entertainment Films for Your Group, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Films for Your Church Groups, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Films Available Without Charge From Michiga Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: You Your Job and Your company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 23: Here's to Your Health, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 24: 1964 Wage reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: 1964 Wage reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 26: 1964 Wage Reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 27: EME Insurance Benefits, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 28: Agreemane Betwee the Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 29: Agreement Betweenthe Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 30: Memorandum of Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 31: Agreement Effective July 9, 1963, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 32: Agreement Effective March 2, 1959, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: Working Agreement Effective March 2, 1959, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Working Agreement Effective November 22, 1957, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 35: Working Agreement Effective June 6, 1960, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 36: Agreemane Betwee the Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 37: Working Agreement Effective October 21, 1955, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 38: Agreemane Betwee the Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 39: Agreement Effective July 9, 1963, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 40: Agreement Effective November 22, 1957, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 41: 1961 Wage Reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 42: 1961 Wage Reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 43: Agreement Effective June 6, 1960, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 44: Working Agreement Effective November 7, 1956, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 45: Agreement Effective June 6, 1960, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 46: Agreemane Betwee the Communications Workers of America and Michigan Bell Telephone Company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 47: 1961 Wage reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 48: Agreement Effective July 9, 1963, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 49: Agreement Effective November 22, 1957, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 50: Agreement Effecive March 2, 1959, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Item 51: 1962 Wage Reopener Agreement, Publication (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Box 46, Folder (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: How to Have a Good Telephone Voice, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Faculty Conference report, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: You Your Job and Your ompany, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: American Telephone and Telegraph company, Publication (Box 46, Folder 3)